jostens.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy

|    
  
|  |   
[Legal Notices](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/legal.asp) ::   
**Jostens Privacy Policy  
Effective February 24, 2016**  
| 

**What's been updated?** We have added links to Canadian and European online tools to opt out of interest-based ads, and added language regarding the geographical location of our servers.

**_Introduction_**

Jostens, Inc., located at 3601 Minnesota Drive, Suite 400, Minneapolis, MN 55435, United States of America, and its corporate affiliates (collectively, " **Jostens** ," " **we** ," " **our** ," **or** " **us** ") are your most trusted partners in celebrating moments that matter, and we value that trust. This Privacy Policy (the " **Policy** ") explains how we collect and use information through jostens.com, services available through jostens.com such as Yearbook Avenue and YearTech Online, and our other websites, applications, widgets, services, and interactive properties on which this Policy appears (each, a " **Property** "), and your choices with respect to our collection and use of information. This Policy applies to information we collect through Properties regardless of how accessed or used; email or electronic newsletters; offline means such as telephone and traditional mail; and any other means or applications you use to connect with us.

This Policy is subject to the Jostens [Terms of Use](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/terms.asp). Each time that you access or use a Property, you signify that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by the [Terms of Use](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/terms.asp) and this Policy. If you do not agree to the [Terms of Use](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/terms.asp) or this Policy, you must discontinue using our Properties.

**_Privacy Policy Summary_**

The following is a high-level summary of how we collect and use information. For more details on our collection and use practices, please read our [full Privacy Policy](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/privacy.asp#fullprivacypolicy).

| **_What information do you collect from and about me?_** |   | We collect personal information and other information from you (including content you provide such as photographs) through your use of this Property, through contacts with our customer service and sales associates, from our customers such as schools, and/or through third parties acting on our behalf such as our independent sales representatives. The information you provide us may include information about yourself, such as your name and contact information, as well as information about others, such as through "send-to-a friend" features. We receive information from third parties such as our customers, our partners, and other trusted sources. We also collect information from third party services, e.g., social networking providers, where you integrate your use of a Property with a third party.  
---|---|---  
  
**_What information do you collect when I access and use a Property?_** |   | Like most websites and services, we and our third party service providers and advertisers use various technologies, including without limitation cookies, flash cookies, HTML5 cookies, tracking pixels, web beacons, and embedded scripts, to make our Properties work and to learn more about our users and their likely interests. We also receive certain information from your device itself, such as IP address and/or device token. If enabled on your device, we use geolocation to provide you with customized or geographically-specific content. We don't respond to browser-based "do not track" headers.   
---|---|---  
  
**_What do you do with collected information?_** |   | We use information we collect to communicate with you about our products or services; to manufacture and produce our products such as yearbooks; to process orders and support our commerce solutions; to provide, manage and improve our Properties, products, services and business; in connection with promotions such as sweepstakes and contests; for us and our service providers to provide services and deliver content; to comply with legal requirements and protect you, Jostens, and others; and in connection with corporate events such as a sale of the business. We use information provided by schools to provide our products and services and as otherwise allowed under this Policy except where a school has restricted our rights to use provided information, and we will not sell or rent such information to any third party. We share your personal information with certain of our partners if you have given us permission to share it with that partner. Except as prohibited by applicable law, we also use your information to personalize your user experience, to improve our Properties, products and services, for fraud prevention, to provide reporting, and for other historical, statistical or research and analysis purposes. If you are outside the US, you give us consent to transfer it to the US.  
---|---|---  
  
**_What choices do I have with respect to your collection and use of information?_** |   | You can withdraw your consent to receive promotional communications from us at any time. If you choose not to provide us with the right to use personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the product, service or information you requested. You can use third party sites, services and apps (links are in our full Privacy Policy) to opt out of the collection of your information from certain third parties, such as Google and other third party advertising service providers (if you clear your cookies, you'll need to opt out again). You can also review and update your personal information in our possession.   
---|---|---  
  
**_What else should I know?_** |   | Our Properties contain third party links, and we are not responsible for those linked sites and services. We do not collect information from children under 13 through our Properties without verifiable parental consent. If you live in California, you have additional rights which we describe in our full Privacy Policy. We update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Feel free to contact us with any privacy-related questions you have using the contact information in our full Privacy Policy.  
---|---|---  
  
**_Full Privacy Policy_**

**1.    Information We Collect From and About You.**

| 

**A**.

| 

**Information Provided to Us.**

_Information from You_. We collect personal information (information that identifies you as an individual) and other information from you through your use of this Property. Examples of the type of information we collect include, but are not limited to, your name, e-mail address, age, gender, the name of the school you attend, billing and/or shipping address, phone number, payment account information, your preferences and interests, and other information about you. We also collect information that you provide to Jostens directly, such as through your contact with our customer service representatives or sales associates, or that you provide to Jostens via Jostens independent sales representatives. 

_User Content._ If you use this Property to submit photographs, user profiles, audiovisual materials, questions, comments or other content (collectively, " **User Content** "), we can reproduce, publish, distribute or otherwise use submitted User Content in any media or format currently existing or later developed. Certain personal information, such as your name and email address, can be publicly displayed along with and/or associated with your User Content. Please think carefully before deciding what information you share as User Content. Please note that we do not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. We are not responsible for the accuracy, use or misuse of any User Content that you provide. If you provide us with any ideas, comments, suggestions, or other feedback related to Jostens' products, services or business, you grant us a perpetual, royalty-free, worldwide right to use it for any purpose related to our business without compensation to you. Please note that your use of Properties through which you can provide User Content is subject to our [Terms of Use](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/terms.asp).

_Information You Provide About Others_. If you initiate a communication to someone else through a Property such as through a "send-to-a-friend" feature, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we expressly advise otherwise. Please be aware that your name and/or email address could be included in any send-to-a-friend communication.

_Information from Schools and Other Third Parties_. In the course of our business and in providing our products and services, we receive personal information about individuals from our customers and partners, including schools.

We also acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information that you provided or we collected automatically, such as information to validate or update your address or other demographic and lifestyle information.

_Information from Social Networking and Third Party Services_. Functionality on a Property can permit interactions with social networking and other third party services (" **Social Features** "). Examples of Social Features include enabling you to "like" or "share" content or to log into a Property using your third party service username and password. If you connect your Jostens account with a third party service provider, it may share information about you with us such as your public profile, e-mail address and friend list. If you choose to "like" or share content, that information and other information about you may be publicly displayed. You should review the privacy policy of that third party service provider and check your privacy settings through that provider. If you post information on a social networking or third party service that references Jostens or its products or services (e.g., via a Twitter hashtag), your post may be cross-published on a Property.  
  
---|---  

**B**.

| 

**Information Collected as You Access and Use a Property**. Like most websites and applications, we and our third party service providers and advertisers use cookies and similar technologies to make our websites and applications work, and to learn more about our users and their likely interests as well as information relating to their visits and interactions with a Property. These technologies include cookies, flash cookies, HTML5 cookies, tracking pixels, web beacons, and embedded scripts (collectively, " **Tracking Technologies** "). We also collect information regarding your web browser or device, and collect geolocation information where you have allowed us or a third party advertiser or service provider to do so.

_Web Browser or Device Information_. We and our service providers collect information sent by your web browser or device, including your IP address, and other information that does not identify you personally such as a device or browser token, the date and time of your visit, information about your web browser or device type, etc. The information received depends on the settings on your web browser or device. If you have created a user identity or profile on one of your visits to a Property, we link the information provided by your browser or device to information that identifies you personally and use it for the purposes described in this Policy. Please review the settings of your web browser or device if you want to learn and change what information is sent by your browser or device. 

_"Do Not Track" Headers_. "Do Not Track" (DNT) is a web browser setting which lets the websites you visit know that you do not want them collecting information about you. We do not respond to DNT settings or signals.

_Geolocation Information_. We use your device's location services to determine your coarse (network-based) and fine (GPS-based) location via your device in order to provide you with customized or geographically-specific content. For example, our ReplayIt® app uses location services to provide users with a list of schools in the user's geographic area to make it easier for users to select an affiliated school. You can control whether your device allows applications to use location services through the mobile device settings for your device. ReplayIt users can turn off these location services within the App by selecting the option to turn off location services in the application bar or other available functionality.

_Cookies_. A cookie is a data file placed on a computer. We use both "session cookies" and "persistent cookies" to collect information for record keeping purposes, to make it easier for you to use a Property, and to customize information that is presented to you through a Property. Session cookies are used to store information while a user accesses a Property, and expire when the user closes his/her browser "session." Persistent cookies store information across sessions (e.g., to make it easier to log into a Property) and stay on your computer until the expiration date set in the cookie (e.g., at the end of a calendar month) or until you delete it. We also use HTML5 local storage ("HTML5 cookies"), which is a newer, faster and more secure cookie technology used with the HTML5 web language. Like traditional cookies, HTML5 local storage can be used as session storage or persistent storage. We also use "Flash cookies," locally-stored data files used to personalize your use of a Property through Adobe Flash technologies. Flash cookies can also be used by our third party service providers to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from standard browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored.

_Web Beacons_. We use small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as "1x1 GIFs," "clear GIFs," "single-pixel GIFs," "pixel tags," "JavaScript tags," "web bugs," and "action tags") on a Property or in our email communications to you. We use web beacons for a number of purposes, such as to track browser types, to track the search terms and domain names that bring visitors to our Property, to count visitors to a Property, to monitor how users navigate a Property, and to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or how many particular links or content elements were actually viewed.

_Embedded Scripts_. We use embedded scripts, which is programming code designed to collect information about how visitors interact with a Property, such as the referring website which linked them to a Property and the manner in which they use a Property. Embedded scripts are downloaded onto your device's cache from our web server or a third party service provider and are deactivated or deleted following the end of your session once your browser cache is cleared.  
  
---|---  
  
**2**. | 

**How We Use and Share Information You Provide and We Collect**. When you provide us with your contact information in connection with a particular activity, product or service, you expressly consent to our communicating with you about our products or services. Jostens uses information collected from or about you, including personal information, User Content, and usage information, to allow you to participate in a Property and its features, to provide you with Jostens products and services, to operate our business, for any other purposes as disclosed to you at the time you provide your information, with your consent, and as disclosed to you in this Policy. We keep your personal information for the purposes for which it was originally collected (or to which you have subsequently consented) and for other legitimate purposes (such as regulatory compliance), as permitted or required by applicable law.

Jostens' servers are located in the United States; if you are located outside of the United States you consent to our storage of your information on servers located in the United States.

_To Process Orders._ If you visit a Property for the purposes of conducting a purchase transaction, we use information for purposes such as the following: 

  * to take, verify, process and deliver your order, process or obtain payment, verify your tax or tax exempt status, contest chargebacks, and determine your credit eligibility;
  * to send you notices from time to time relating to your account, your purchases and orders;
  * to determine your geographical location for compliance, security, anti-piracy, and fraud prevention purposes;
  * to provide you, to the extent permitted by applicable law, with a personalized shopping experience;
  * for warranty, technical support or similar purposes;
  * to establish an account for future purchases by you;
  * to facilitate subscription renewals; and
  * to provide you with effective customer service (which to the extent and in a manner permitted by applicable law includes contacting users in connection with their use, or ceasing to use or abandoning a transaction through a Property) and/or technical support.

_Use of Anonymous Information_. We use anonymous information collected by or provided to us for purposes such as the following: 

  * to personalize and support your use of a Property, our products and services, and/or the services of our customers and partners;
  * to improve a Property, the customer and consumer experience, and our products and services;
  * for fraud prevention purposes, such as device fingerprinting;
  * to identify actions or transactions as originating through an affiliate marketing, channel partner, or referral program;
  * to deliver targeted advertisements on a Property and other websites and/or commerce solutions;
  * to provide reporting to our current and prospective partners and service providers; and
  * for other historical, statistical or research and analysis purposes.

In addition, we can "de-identify" personal information by removing any information that identifies you specifically, and use the resulting anonymous information for the purposes set forth above.

_Use of School Information_. Jostens uses personal information about individuals received from or on behalf of our school customers to create and promote products and services for the benefit of the school and to customize products as requested by purchasers, and can use it for other purposes permitted under this Policy except as prohibited by applicable law and except to the extent the providing party or the data subject has restricted our rights to use provided personal information. Jostens will not sell or rent personal information provided by schools to any third party.

_To Provide, Manage and Improve our Properties, Products, Services and Our Business and to Deliver Content_. We use information that we collect and obtain to provide our goods and services, to administer a Property, and for other lawful business purposes. These include the manufacture and printing of products, such as yearbooks, announcements, memory books and jewelry which can contain personal information such as names and photos. We also use the information that we collect and obtain about you to measure and improve our Properties, products and services; to help up maintain the accuracy of information in our systems; to customize certain features of a Property, to deliver relevant content and to provide you with an enhanced experience based on the type of device you are using. Except where prohibited by applicable law, we use information to send you promotional communications by email, regular mail, and other methods regarding our products and services, and may serve advertising on a Property that we believe is likely to be of interest to you. You can manage whether and how you receive such communications as described in the "[Your Choices](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/privacy.asp#yourchoices)" section of this Policy.

To the extent permitted by law, we may use third party advertising service providers, including networks, data exchanges, ad servers, analytics providers and others to serve ads regarding our products and services. These third party service providers utilize Tracking Technologies to collect certain information about your visits to our Property and third party websites, your interaction with our Property or those websites, and the products and services offered by us, our partners, and others. We and our partners use this information, as well as information received from other sources, for marketing analysis, for quality improvement purposes, and to provide you with customized content and offers. We do not control Tracking Technologies used by third parties, and their use is governed by their own privacy policies. For more information on online advertising, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). We also use Google Analytics along with audience data (e.g., age, gender and interests of users) to better understand users' visits to and use of our Properties, and to optimize served content. You can manage the use of Tracking Technologies and Google Analytics to collect information about you as described in the "[Your Choices](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/privacy.asp#yourchoices)" section of this Policy.

_In Connection with Promotions_. We offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a " **Promotion** ") that require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you agree to the official rules for that Promotion. If you enter a Promotion, the information you provide through registration can be used and disclosed as set forth in this Policy, as well as in connection with the administration of such Promotion and as required by applicable law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules.

_With Certain Partners._ We may give you the opportunity to receive marketing and promotional offers and/or other content from certain of our partners (collectively, " **Partner Offers** "). If you agree to receive Partner Offers, we share your personal information (excluding payment information) with that partner, and that partner may send you Partner Offers. Our partner's use of your information is governed by that partner's privacy policy.

_For Us and Our Service Providers to Provide Services and Deliver Content_. We use third party service providers to perform certain services in connection with our business, such as fulfilling and processing orders, payment processing, verifying and validating information, hosting all or part of Properties, providing website usage analytics, list management, sending communications, customer support, providing marketing assistance and data analysis, and providing other administrative services. We provide our service providers access to information, including personal information, only for the purpose of carrying out services on our behalf. Certain service providers use Tracking Technologies to collect and store information about you and your use of a Property, and combine this information with information they collect from other sources. If you access a Property through a mobile device or application, certain of your information is sharted with the mobile carrier or application provider. Information provided through a portion of a Property that is hosted by a Jostens service provider may be stored on our systems, and/or the systems, of our service provider, and will be provided to Jostens and/or processed by that service provider for Jostens' business purposes. 

_To Comply with Legal Requirements and Protect You, Jostens and Others_. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may disclose information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law or a regulatory requirement; to comply with governmental, administrative or judicial process, requirement or order, such as a subpoena or court order; to cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental investigations (without necessarily requiring the law enforcement or government agency requesting the information to formally serve us with a subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce a contract; to protect the legal rights, property, or safety of Jostens, its corporate affiliates, and their respective employees, clients, partners and agents, other users or the public in general; or to protect your vital interests if determined necessary by us. In addition, we review our server logs for security purposes, such as detecting intrusions into our network. If we suspect criminal activity, we share our server logs – which contain visitors' IP addresses – with the appropriate investigative authorities who use that information to trace and identify individuals. We also reserve the right to report to appropriate law enforcement or government agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe are in violation of applicable laws, rules or regulations without providing notice.

_In Connection with Corporate Events_. If one of our corporate affiliates or a third party has acquired all or part of our business, specific assets or the business of one of our operating divisions through which you have provided information to us, e.g., as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, insolvency, dissolution or liquidation, ownership of your personal information will transfer to that company. In that event, the acquiring company's use of your personal information will still be governed by this Policy and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.  
  
---|---  

**3**. | 

**Your Choices Regarding the Collection and Use of Information**. When you provide personal information to us, you control whether you would like to receive further communications from us and/or from our clients and partners about products or services of interest. You have the right to withdraw your consent.

If you decide you no longer want to receive marketing communications from us: 

  * _To unsubscribe from marketing emails_ , click the "unsubscribe" link in the commercial electronic message you received. Alternatively, you can e-mail us at [remove@jostens.com](mailto:remove@jostens.com) and specify in your e-mail which consent you are revoking.
  * _To unsubscribe from marketing mail,_ email us at [remove@jostens.com](mailto:remove@jostens.com) and provide the name and mailing address of the person to be unsubscribed and the associated school name (both are required to ensure we can process your request). If you change mailing addresses after unsubscribing from physical marketing mailings, you will need to unsubscribe your new mailing address.

Please note that Jostens' clients and partners (such as schools and independent sales representatives) may also send you marketing communications regarding Jostens products unless you unsubscribe from their communications. If you give us permission to add your contact information to the mailing list of one of our clients or partners and later withdraw your permission from Jostens, you will have to unsubscribe from that client or partner's mailings as well. 

If you choose not to provide us with the right to use personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the product, service or information you requested. We use certain personal information to create the products we offer, such as jewelry, announcements, yearbooks and memory books. If you elect not to give us the right to use personal information in connection with the creation of our products, it may result in the omission of a person's name, picture, and/or other information from a yearbook or memory book, or the inability for us to create a customized product.

  * _Interest-Based Ads._ You can view a list of third party service providers participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") which serve interest-based ads through your computer using web viewing data collected from your computer, and/or opt-out of such collection, by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. Please note that opting out does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising from a service provider, but that the service provider will no longer deliver interest-ads based on predictions about your interests generated from web viewing data.
    * Canadian users can opt out of receiving interest-based ads by using the opt-out tool available through the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada's website at [http://www.youradchoices.ca](http://www.youradchoices.ca/).

    * European users can opt out of receiving interest-based ads by using the opt-out tool for their country available through the "Your Online Choices" website operated by the EU Internet advertising industry, located at [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

  * _Mobile Device Users._ Mobile device users can use the DAA's AppChoices app to view a list of DAA-participating third party service providers which serve interest-based ads through your mobile device using app usage data collected from your mobile device, and/or opt-out of such collection. Download the app by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices/>. Please note that opting out does not mean you will no longer receive ads on your mobile device from a service provider, but that the service provider will no longer deliver interest-based ads based on predictions generated from app usage data.

  * _Google Analytics._ You can install Google Analytics' opt-out browser add-on by visiting <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. You can opt out of receiving interest-based Google advertisements, or customize the ads you receive from Google, by visiting <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

_Cookies._ If you accept a session or persistent cookie, you can delete it at any time through your web browser (e.g., as soon as you leave our Property). If you do not wish to receive cookies or wish to manage when you accept cookies in general, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Your use of the features and functionality of this Property will be limited if you set your browser to reject cookies. If you opt out of having your information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tools, your existing display advertising cookie(s) will be deleted and a new cookie will attempt to be placed that instructs service providers not to track your future activities when that cookie is detected (a "no-track" cookie). If your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit our opt-out page, a "no-track" cookie cannot be set on your computer. Also, if you subsequently erase "do-no-track" cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs only apply to the specific computer and browser on which the opt-out cookie is applied.

  * _Flash Cookies._ To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please visit [www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html).

---|---  

**4**. | 

**Reviewing and Updating Your Personal Information**. If you would like to review, correct or challenge your personal information, or if you are the parent or legal guardian of a minor and would like to review, correct or challenge that minor's personal information, please contact us by postal mail addressed to Jostens, Inc., ATTN: Privacy Department, 3601 Minnesota Drive, Suite 400, Minneapolis, MN 55343, United States of America, or by e-mail at [privacy@jostens.com](mailto:privacy@jostens.com). If you contact us, we may, for your protection, ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In most cases, we will provide the access you request and correct or delete any inaccurate personal information you discover. We reserve the right, however, to limit or deny your request to the extent permitted by applicable law if the disclosure could lead to a breach of applicable law and regulation, such as in case of any legal obligation to retain certain data, or if you have failed to verify your identity to our satisfaction.  
  
---|---  
  
**5**. | 

**Third Party Content and Links**. Some Jostens Properties contain third party content, and those third parties can collect usage information and/or your device identifier when their information is served to the Property and presented to you. In addition, certain Properties contain links to other web sites that are operated and controlled by third parties that we do not control, including third party commerce solutions. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any of these third parties or third party web-sites. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement, you connect with a third party web-site. Third party web sites can send their own cookies, JavaScript or other web technologies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and have their own published privacy policies. Jostens encourages you to read the privacy statements of all third party web sites before submitting any personal information on or through those sites.  
  
---|---  
  
**6**. | 

**Consent to Transfer Information to the United States**. If this Property is a website or commerce solution, it is operated in the United States and is intended for users located in the United States. If this Property is a software application, it is intended for users located in the United States. If you are located anywhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including personal information, will be transferred to, processed in, and stored in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your personal information can be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to the laws of the United States. By using a Property or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer, processing, and storage of your information in the United States. You are also consenting to the application of United States federal and Minnesota state law in all matters concerning the Property and this Policy.  
  
---|---  
  
**7**. | 

**Children's Privacy**. Our Properties are intended for use by general audiences. We do not collect personal information from children younger than the age of thirteen (13) through a Property without verifiable parental consent, and we will delete any personal information collected through a Property that we later determine to be from a user younger than the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If you believe a child under the age of thirteen (13) has disclosed personal information to us without verifiable parental consent, please contact us via the information provided in the "[Contact Us](http://www.jostens.com/apps/shop/help/shared/privacy.asp#contactus)" section of this Policy.  
  
---|---  
  
**8**. | 

**Security**. We have implemented safeguards reasonably designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. It is important that you understand, however, that no commerce solution, website, application, database or system is completely secure or "hacker proof," and we cannot anticipate all potential misuse of your information. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and your use of a Property indicates that you are willing to assume this risk.  
  
---|---  
  
**9**. | 

**Your California Privacy Rights**.

_Removal of Posted Information by Minors_. Under California law, Jostens customers who are California residents under 18 and are registered users of a Property can remove, or request and obtain removal of, content or information posted by the customer on this Property. Certain Properties offer functionality to remove posted content. If functionality to remove posted content is not available, California residents under 18 can request the removal of posted content and information by emailing [remove@jostens.com](mailto:remove@jostens.com) with "California Minor Content Removal Request" in the subject line and in the body of your message. Please specify in your request the Property to which your request relates and the specific information or content you posted for which you are requesting removal. Please note that the removal of content and information does not ensure the complete or comprehensive removal of the posted content or information

_Information Shared With Third Parties_. Under California's "Shine the Light" law, Jostens customers who are California residents can request certain information once per calendar year regarding the types of information shared by Jostens with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and the identities of those third parties. If you are a California resident, email requests to [privacy@jostens.com](mailto:privacy@jostens.com) with "California Privacy Information Request" in the subject line and in the body of your message. Please also specify in your request the Jostens company to which your request pertains, otherwise we will treat your request as pertaining to Jostens, Inc. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.  
  
---|---  
  
**10**. | 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**. This Policy will be updated from time to time to reflect, among other things, changes in applicable laws, rules or regulations, changes in our data collection practices, and/or changes to our business or services. Changes to our Policy will become effective when posted and will only apply to information collected on and after the effective date of the revised Policy. If revisions to the Policy materially affect how we use personal information collected from you prior to the date of the revised Policy, then we will request that you opt-in to the revised Policy. We will make an updated version of this Policy accessible through the Property with a revised effective date, to let you know that we updated the Policy.  
  
---|---
